#### Contact

knugentconley@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karen-conley-dnp-rn (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing

Hospitals

**Patient Safety** 

#### **Publications**

Nurse Manager Engagement: Strategies to Enhance and Maintain Engagement

One CNO's Journey in Pursuit of a Nurse on the Hospital Board

# Karen Conley DNP, RN, NEA-BC

Vice President, Clinical Services at Kyruus

Greater Boston Area

## Summary

Dynamic Nurse Executive with a career built on a record of success across diverse range of organizations and environments. Clinically trained as an expert Oncology Nurse with a keen focus on the experience of the patient and family. Proven business and operational skills leading all major hospital and ambulatory service lines in both community and academic medical center settings. Focusing now on improving healthcare access throughout the United States. Committed collaborator with all interdisciplinary team members to navigate together the ever changing healthcare environment.

Practices each day reflecting on these words of Florence Nightingale "Let whoever is in charge keep this simple question in her head...how can I provide for the right thing to be always done?"

# Experience

**Kyruus** 

1 year 11 months

Vice President, Clinical Services August 2019 - Present (1 year)

Boston, MA

Senior Director, Clinical Services September 2018 - August 2019 (1 year)

Boston, Massachusetts

Organization of Nurse Leaders for MA, RI, CT and NH Treasurer Board Of Directors 2016 - 2018 (2 years)

Newton-Wellesley Hospital SVP Patient Care Services and Chief Nursing Officer 2015 - 2017 (2 years)

Newton, MA

Massachusetts Board of Registration for Pharmacy Board Member 2015 - 2017 (2 years)

Boston, Massachusetts

### Brigham and Women's Hospital

Associate Chief Nurse and VP for Women's Health and Neonatology 2012 - 2015 (3 years)

Boston, MA

Responsible for the Connors Center for Women and Newborns. Services include antepartum, labor, birth, post partum, NICU, GYN surgery, GYN oncology. Supporting a service of 500+ nurses and over 8,500 births annually.

Quincy Medical Center SVP Patient Care Services/CNO 2009 - 2012 (3 years) Quincy, MA

Member of the senior leadership team responsible for nursing, respiratory, cardiology, pharmacy, rehabilitation, radiology and laboratory services. Quincy Medical Center became part of the Steward Health Care System in October 2011.

## South Shore Hospital

Director of Medical/Surgical and Critical Care Services 2005 - 2009 (4 years)

Responsible for all inpatient nursing units as well as the IV team, Cardiac Cath Lab and Dialysis.

Dana-Farber Cancer Institute Program Manager for Pediatric Oncology 2000 - 2005 (5 years)

Leader for the Jimmy Fund Clinic serving the outpatient pediatric population at Dana-Farber. Also was the administrative liaison for the Adult and Pediatric Patient and Family Advisory Councils

Brigham and Women's Hospital Nurse Manager 1989 - 2001 (12 years)

Responsible for six inpatient hematology/oncology and bone marrow transplant units.

# Education

Boston College BSN, Nursing · (1984 - 1989)

Northeastern University
MS, Nursing Administration · (1994 - 1996)

MGH Institute of Health Professions

DNP, Executive Nursing Practice · (2010 - 2012)

Harvard Business School Executive Education Healthcare Leadership · (2014 - 2015)